

Muhammad Ihsan

Web Devoleper

Medan, Medan City, North Sumatra, Indonesia

Hi, I'm Ihsan! I'm a web developer experience in web-developments. In a nutshell, I create websites that right now still in development. I manage everything from website navigation and layout, web hosting and security architecture. Even though it's still using free hosting like github and heroku. My expertise lies within front-end web apps, and the main languages in my tech stack are JavaScript, React, and of course HTML/CSS. I'm a lifelong learner and love to read, run, and find new bubble tea shops anywhere.

ihsanzack@gmail.com

https://www.instagram.com/ihsanzack/

https://jek-san.github.io/ihsan-profile/

https://wa.me/+6288293547354

Skills

Tech Stack









CSS

django Django RestFramework

Work Experience



Internship Student PLN UNIT PELAKSANA PELAYANAN PELANGGAN

August 2021 - October 2022 Jakarta, Indonesia

Cdatacomm

Network Engineer PT.Datacomm Diangraha

January 2020 - March 2020 Jakarta, Indonesia Make plans for electrical substations per city area.

Study the operation flow of the SCADA system between substations.

Make a recapitulation of the minutes of field officers' activities

Learn the operation of the distribution system of PT. PLN.

Make reports for simplification of drawings of electrical wiring substations.

Perform installation, Integration, Dismantle, Migration, Migration Satelite, Insert Module, Upgrade Module, Cut-Off Link, Maintenance and Service of Metro-E Indosat

Education



2016 - 2022

Institut Technology PLN

Bachelor Degree of Informatics Engineering

Licenses & Certifications



Microsoft Certified Azzure Al Fundamental

Microsoft

wY3E6-2FM8 Issued July 2022 · No Expiration Date



Microsoft Office Specialist

Microsoft

s5Hu-XLKe Issued March 2017 · No Expiration Date

Achievement

Ketua Pelaksana Futsal Himanad

2018

Jakarta, Indonesia

Powered by CakeResume